Guide to the National Education Association-Special Collections records, 1857-2015 NEA1007.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Joy Elmer Morgan Papers, 1916-1962; Series 5; Morgan, Joy Elmer; 7 Linear Feet
  - What Religion Means to Me, March 23, 1935; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 8)
  - What the American School Means to Me - Statement Written by a 1933 Senior, Undated; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 9)
  - What the Modern School Expects of the Child, Undated; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 10)
  - What to Read and How to Read it, Undated; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 11)
  - Why the Public School?, Undated; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 12)
  - Why the Public Should Support its High Schools, 1934; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 13)
  - World Good Will Day Message to Young People, 1935; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 14)
  - Writings, 1906-1918; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 15)
  - Writings, 1958; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 16)
  - Writings About Mr. Crabtree, 1932-1937; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 17)
  - Writings on Christmas and Holidays, Undated; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 18)
  - Writings, Peru - Nebraska, 1906-1916; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 19)
  - Writings - University Place, Bloomington Guide Rock, Nebraska, 1911-1917; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 20)
  - Your Mind and Narcotics - Allied Youth, Novemeber 1935; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 21)
  - Youth and Crisis in American Life With Particular Reference to College Journalism, February 17, 1934; Series 5 (Box 3314, Folder 22)
- Organization History, 1857-2015; Series 6; 4.5 Linear Feet
  Series is arranged alphanumerically then chronologically.
  Series contains material that documents the history of the NEA, though not always as primary sources; in some cases, this means secondary sources such as chronologies, biographies and celebratory material. In other cases, it means photocopies or transcriptions of original documents. The material includes biographical material, chronologies of the organization, illustrations, flyers, historical statistics, photographs, scripts and scrapbooks. The series also contains the records of the Centennial Committee, formed to celebrate the 1957 Centennial of the NEA, a photo album created to commemorate the inauguration of Dr. Lambert as Executive Secretary and the notes and papers of Dr. Edgar Wesley, the author of "NEA: The First Hundred Years" as well as four scrapbooks of photographs and memorabilia sent from local and state affiliates to commemorate the centennial celebration. A fifth scrapbook seems to have been put together for the Centennial Celebration, but without the connection to the affiliates.
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration Exhibit, Undated; Series (Box 4867, Folder 49)
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration Exhibit Bicentennial Plague, January 9, 1976; Series (Box 4867, Folder 50)
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration Convention Photos, 1956-1964; Series (Box 4868, Folder 2)
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration Convention, Contennial Song, Birthday Party, 1906-1907; Series (Box 4868, Folder 3)
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration International Inters, May 2007; Series (Box 4868, Folder 4)
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration ATA Historical Events, 1965-1979; Series (Box 4868, Folder 5)
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration Hand Written Papers, 1865-1936; Series (Box 4868, Folder 6)
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration Historical Staff, 1895-1995; Series (Box 4868, Folder 7)
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration Items Given Casey Communications Plus, May 5, 2007; Series (Box 4868, Folder 8)
  - 150th Anniversary Celebration National Symphony, 1957; Series (Box 4868, Folder 1)
  - 1857 Secretary - William Everts Sheldon, 1865-1919; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 1)
    Material is all photocopies
  - The 1979 Democratic Gala, September 26 1979; series 6 (Box 4502, Folder 14)
  - AASA Convention TV guide, Undated; Series 6 (Box 4931, Folder 2)
  - Accomplishments, ca. 1950-1969; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 2)
  - Activities and Events, 1952-1959; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 3)
  - Affiliates/Organizations, ca. 1968; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 4)
  - American Council on Education, 1929-1931; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 5)
  - The Athenaeum; Birthplace of NEA August 26, 1857, 1969, 1982; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 6)
    Includes color slides
  - Author of Preamble; Constitution Committee Chair, Daniel Barnard Hagar, 1865-1884; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 7)
    Contains photocopies only
  - Awards/Ceremonies, 1962, 1967; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 8)
  - Before and After Brown in Prince Edward County, VA [print from web], September-October, 2013; Series 6 (Box 3970, Folder 9)
  - "BRAG" Materials, 1947-1981; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 9)
  - Building Renovation Update, May 1987 - April 1991; series 6 (Box 4310, Folder 1)
  - Building To Strengthen Public Education, October 1991; Series 6 (Box 4931, Folder 5)
  - The Call, 1857, 1879; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 10)
    Includes only photocopies and reproductions
  - Centennial Celebration Scrapbook - Alabama thru Indiana, 1957; Series 6 (Box 3265, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Celebration Scrapbook - Iowa thru New Hampshire, 1957; Series 6 (Box 3265, Folder 2)
  - Centennial Celebration Scrapbook - New Jersey thru Oregon, 1957; Series 6 (Box 3265, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Celebration Scrapbook - Pennsylvania thru Wyoming, 1957; Series 6 (Box 3265, Folder 4)
  - Centennial History [1/2], 1955-1957; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 11)
  - Centennial History [2/2], 1955-1957; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 12)
  - Centennial History Committee, 1955-1974; Series 6 (Box 3000, Folder 13)
  - Centennial - Presentation Template, 1957; Series 6 (Box 3317, Folder 2)
  - Chairman James Little Enos, undated; Series 6 (Box 3001, Folder 1)
  - Committees/Departments, 1952-1991; Series 6 (Box 3002, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Regarding " A Special Mission", 1985-1987; series 6 (Box 4310, Folder 2)
  - [Crisis in Education], 1954-1959; Series 6 (Box 3517, Folder 6)
  - Data - NEA/Teachers, Ca. 1872-1986; Series 6 (Box 3002, Folder 3)
  - The Dallas Times Herald Dallas Apologizes, July 5, 1968; Series 6 (Box 4931, Folder 6)
  - The Dedication of the Headquarters Building of the NEA, October 1991; series 6 (Box 4378, Folder 9)
  - Dissertation by Mildred Sandison Fenner - "The National Education Association 1892-1942" Title Page-Page 149, June 3, 1942; Series 6 (Box 3302, Folder 1)
  - Dissertation by Mildred Sandison Fenner - "The National Education Association 1892-1942" Page150-Page 299, June 3, 1942; Series 6 (Box 3302, Folder 2)
  - Dissertation by Mildred Sandison Fenner - "The National Education Association 1892-1942" Page 300-Page 444, June 3, 1942; Series 6 (Box 3302, Folder 3)
  - Drawings - Events in NEA History, Ca. 1957; Series 6 (Box 3002, Folder 4)
  - Educational Policies Commission, March 1937; Series 6 (Box 4931, Folder 7)
  - Executive Correspondence Index (duplicates), 1986; Series 6 (Box 3002, Folder 5)
  - Expressions of the Presidents Approving the Concept of Federal Aid for Education, Washington 1790 - Roosevelt 1937, April, 1937; Series 6 (Box 3534, Folder 10)
  - Fact Sheets, Ca. 1985; Series 6 (Box 3530, Folder 1)
  - First Elected President Zalmon Richards (1857-1858), 1885; Series 6 (Box 3002, Folder 6)
    Photocopies only
  - Founders of the NEA (A manuscript - Norton, Albert Ches.), 1959-1960; Series 6 (Box 3002, Folder 7)
  - General Information, 1950-1983; Series 6 (Box 3002, Folder 8)
  - Growth of the Association Idea by Willard Givens, 1955; Series 6 (Box 3970, Folder 10)
  - History (NEA), 1863-1907; Series 6 (Box 3002, Folder 9)
  - History of the NEA Collective Bargaining Program 1957-1998, April 2015; series 6 (Box 4310, Folder 3)
  - Historical Chronology and Pictures, 1857-1955; Series 6 (Box 3002, Folder 10)
  - A Historic Chapter in American Education comes to a Close, July 6, 1989; Series 6 (Box 4931, Folder 11)
  - Historical/Significant Papers, 1907-1984; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 1)
  - Histories, 1957-1983; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 2)
  - History and Organization of the NEA, 1953-1986; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 3)
  - History - NEA, 1922-1967; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 4)
  - Human and Civil Rights Info, 1953-1981; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 5)
  - Histories' Writing of Former Black Associations, 1971, 1980, 1981; Series 6 (Box 4932, Folder 1)
  - The Inauguration of Sam M. Lambert as Executive Secretary of the National Education Association, October 20, 1967; Series 6 (Box 3282, Box 1)
  - Information Bulletin Los Angeles California, 1960; Series 6 (Box 4932, Folder 2)
  - Information on Student Program, 1974-1982; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 6)
  - Instructions For Completing the Attendance Report Form, Undated; Series 6 (Box 4932, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1979 - 1980; series 6 (Box 4502, Folder 15)
  - Kansas City, Missouri Celebrates, 1957; Series 6 (Box 3317, Folder 4)
  - Legislation Activity, 1984; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 7)
  - Lifetime Membership Dinners, 1911-1942; Series 6 (Box 3321, Folder 5)
  - List of NEA Staff, 1920-1969; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 8)
  - [Loose in Box], Undated; Series 6 (Box 4655, Folder 3)
  - [Loose in Box], 2008-2009; Series 6 (Box 4781, Folder 8)
  - [Loose in Box, Response to September 11], 2001; Series 6 (Box 4781, Folder 9)
  - Main Address by William Russell (Read by Thomas Weston Valentine), Undated; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 9)
  - Mayflower Luncheon, November 14, 1958; Series 6 (Box 4932, Folder 4)
  - Membership Tables, 1896-1978; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 10)
  - Membership Record - Treasurer's Department, 1898; Series 6 (Box 3530, Folder 2)
  - [Michigan Legislature - House concurrent resolution No. 36], 1957; Series 6 (Box 3530, Folder 3)
  - [Miscellaneous Pins] [1/6], Undated; Series 6 (Box 4422, Folder 3)
  - [Miscellaneous Pins] [2/6], Undated; Series 6 (Box 4422, Folder 4)
  - [Miscellaneous Pins] [3/6], Undated; Series 6 (Box 4422, Folder 5)
  - [Miscellaneous Pins] [4/6], Undated; Series 6 (Box 4423, Folder 1)
  - [Miscellaneous Pins] [5/6], Undated; Series 6 (Box 4423, Folder 2)
  - [Miscellaneous Pins] [6/6], Undated; Series 6 (Box 4423, Folder 3)
  - National Education Association 150 Years of Advancing Great Public Schools, 2007; Series 6 (Box 4599, Folder 8)
  - NEA Achievements: A Series of Brief Summaries..... 1857-1956 [Revised Copy], January, 1956; Series 6 (Box 3534, Folder 11)
  - The National Education Association, A Special Mission, 1987; Series 6 (Box 4704, Folder 10)
  - NEA-ATA Merger, Silver Anniversary Celebration, 1966; Series 6 (Box 4677, Folder 7)
  - NEA - AFT Fact Sheet, 1978 - 1981; series 6 (Box 4310, Folder 4)
  - NEA 86th Annual Meeting Boston, July 4-8, 1949; Series 6 (Box 4931, Folder 3)
  - NEA Banquets and Pamphlets, 1951, 1952, 1953; Series 6 (Box 4931, Folder 4)
  - NEA Centennial Historian: Dr. Edgar Wesley, Ca. 1956; Series 6 (Box 3003, Folder 11)
  - NEA Centennial Pageant, February 26, 1957; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 1)
  - NEA Chronology, 1858-1984; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 2)
  - NEA - Description, etc..., 1923-1961; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 3)
  - NEA Dedication - General Dedication Committee, July 22, 1959; Series 6 (Box 4931, Folder 9)
  - NEA Dedication - Subcommittee On Local Dedication Activities General, November 1958; Series 6 (Box 4931, Folder 8)
  - NEA Formation Material for 1983 Representative Assembly in Philadelphia, 1857-1892; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 4)
  - NEA Headquarter's History, 1917-1963; series 6 (Box 4310, Folder 5)
  - NEA History, Undated; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 5)
  - NEA History: Loose Items in Box, 1955-1976; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 6)
  - NEA History: Loose Items in Box, 1892-1982; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 7)
  - NEA History Its Development and Program, 1945; Series 6 (Box 4931, Folder 10)
  - [NEA Posters], 1931-1988; Series 6 (Box 3518, Folder 1)
    American Education Week
  - NEA Resolutions Material, Ca. 1930-1955; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 8)
  - NEA: The First Hundred Years & NEA History, 1957; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Accounts of the Formation August 1857, Undated; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 10)
  - The No Taunting Pledge, July 4, 1999; Series 6 (Box 4677, Folder 8)
  - Organizational Structure, 1907-1968; Series 6 (Box 3004, Folder 11)
  - Original Score - "The Time of Their Lives", Undated; Series 6 (Box 3317, Folder 3)
  - Outside Articles - History, 1928-1957; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 1)
  - Panama-Pacific Exposition Day, 1915; Series 6 (Box 4040, Folder 14)
  - Pieces to Follow-Up On, 1857-1986; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings of Convention for Organization, 1857; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 3)
    Copy only
  - Program Activities [1/2], 1933-1971; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 4)
  - Program Activities [2/2], 1933-1971; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 5)
  - Portraits, Undated; Series (Box 4866, Folder 1)
  - Publications, 1935-1974; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 6)
  - R. Tait Mackenzie - Column on Youth Memorial, 1947; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 7)
  - Rights Activities, 1964-1968; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 8)
  - Robert Campbell - Charter Member of the NEA, 1959-1983; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, 1953-1957; Series 6 (Box 3281, Box 1)
  - Snowball Dinner and Dance, Council Rock High School, November 17 1979; series 6 (Box 4502, Folder 16)
  - Special Historical Facts, 1892-1977; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 10)
  - "A Special Mission" Manuscript, 1985; series 6 (Box 4310, Folder 6)
  - Spider-Man and the Fantastic Four in... Brain Drain!, September 2006; Series 6 (Box 4781, Folder 10)
  - Suggested List of Historic Sites and Landmarks Associated with the Development of American Education, 1962; Series 6 (Box 3953, Folder 9)
  - Thomas Weston Valentine, 1857-1945; Series 6 (Box 3005, Folder 11)
  - Timeline of American Education 1839-2000, undated; Series 6 (Box 4092, Folder 1)
  - Visit to Egypt of Town Hall Meeting of the Air, August 2-6, 1949; Series 6 (Box 3317, Folder 5)
  - A Voice for Education NEA Through the Decades, ca. 1984; Series 6 (Box 4992, Folder 2)
- Programs, 1930-2000; Series 7; 19.5 Linear Feet
  series is arranged alphabetically by title and chronologically after that.
  The American Education Week, a one-week observance each year "for the purpose of informing the public of the accomplishments and needs of the public schools and to secure the cooperation and support of the public in meeting those needs," was first called for in 1921 by the NEA Representative Assembly in Des Moines, Iowa.
  Source: "American Education Week-A History" Accessed December 22, 2011 http://www.nea.org/grants/20486.htm Accessed 12/22/2011
  Series contains materials created as part of programs administered by the NEA and it's adminsitrative areas. This includes artifacts from past American Education Weeks, an annual expo "for the purpose of informing the public of the accomplishments and needs of the public schools and to secure the cooperation and support of the public in meeting those needs" as well material from National Teachers Days.
  - A Voice for Education: NEA Through the Decades, 1986; Series 7 (Box 4820, Folder 24)
  - American Education Week, 1930; Series 7 (Box 2780, Folder 1)
  - Addresses and Proceedings of NEA Annual Meetings, 1918-1922; Series 7 (Box 4092, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-"American Education and You: Partners in Our Children's Future" [copy 2], 1981; Series 7 (Box 2780, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Brochure-"Education in the 80s-Preparation for the Future", 1980; Series 7 (Box 2780, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-College and University Packet, 1935; Series 7 (Box 2780, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Form Material, 1940; Series 7 (Box 2780, Folder 5)
  - American Education Week Governor's Proclamations, 1957-1973; Series 7 (Box 4092, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Junior High School Packet, 1939; Series 7 (Box 2780, Folder 6)
  - American Education Week-Leaflet, Stickers, Manual, Poster, Stencil and Promotional Materials, 1944; Series 7 (Box 2780, Folder 7)
  - American Education Week-"Making Democracy Work" Packet, 1949; Series 7 (Box 2780, Folder 8)
  - American Education Week-Notebook [file 1/2], 1952; Series 7 (Box 2780, Folder 9)
  - American Education Week-Notebook [file 2/2], 1952; Series 7 (Box 2781, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week Observance Manual November 11-17, 1984, Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 5)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1942; Series 7 (Box 2781, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1946; Series 7 (Box 2781, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1948; Series 7 (Box 2781, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1948; Series 7 (Box 2781, Folder 5)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1950; Series 7 (Box 2781, Folder 6)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1951; Series 7 (Box 2781, Folder 7)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1952; Series 7 (Box 2781, Folder 8)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1954; Series 7 (Box 2781, Folder 9)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1955; Series 7 (Box 2781, Folder 10)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1956; Series 7 (Box 2782, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1957; Series 7 (Box 2782, Folder 2)
    Audiovisual material was separated from this folder.
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1958; Series 7 (Box 2782, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1959; Series 7 (Box 2782, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1962; Series 7 (Box 2783, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet [copy 2], 1962; Series 7 (Box 2783, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1963; Series 7 (Box 2783, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet [copy 2], 1963; Series 7 (Box 2783, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1965; Series 7 (Box 2783, Folder 5)
    Scope and Contents note
    Contains 1 safety film strip, "American Education Week, November 7-13, 1965"
  - American Education Week-Packet [copy 2], 1965; Series 7 (Box 2783, Folder 6)
    Contains 1 safety film strip, "American Education Week, November 7-13. 1965"
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1964; Series 7 (Box 2784, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1966; Series 7 (Box 2784, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1966; Series 7 (Box 2784, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet [copy 2], 1966; Series 7 (Box 2785, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1967; Series 7 (Box 2785, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet [copy 2], 1967; Series 7 (Box 2785, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1968; Series 7 (Box 2786, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet [copy 2, incomplete], 1968; Series 7 (Box 2786, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1969; Series 7 (Box 2786, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet [copy 2, incomplete], 1969; Series 7 (Box 2786, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1970; Series 7 (Box 2787, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet [copy 2], 1970; Series 7 (Box 2787, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1971; Series 7 (Box 2787, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet [copy 2], 1971; Series 7 (Box 2787, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Packet, 1982; Series 7 (Box 2787, Folder 5)
  - American Education Week-Packet [copy 2], 1982; Series 7 (Box 2787, Folder 6)
  - American Education Week Packet, 1983; Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week Packet, November 17-23, 1985, Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 6)
  - American Education Week Packet, November 13-19, 1988, Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 7)
  - American Education Week Packet, November 12-18, 1989, Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 8)
  - American Education Week Packet, November 11-17, 1990, Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 9)
  - American Education Week Packet, November 17-23, 1991, Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 10)
  - American Education Week Packet, November 15-21, 1992, Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 11)
  - American Education Week Packet, November 13-19, 1994, Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 12)
  - American Education Week Packet, November 12-18. 1995, Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 13)
  - American Education Week Packet, November 16-22, 1997, Series 7 (Box 4423, Folder 14)
  - American Education Week-Packet (incomplete), 1945; Series 7 (Box 2787, Folder 7)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"American Education and You: Partners in Our Children's Future", 1981; Series 7 (Box 2788, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"America's Public Schools: The Subject is Excellence", 1985; Series 7 (Box 2788, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"America's Schools: Invest in Your Future", 1988; Series 7 (Box 2788, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"America's Schools: Invest in Your Future" [copy 2], 1988; Series 7 (Box 2788, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"A Strong Nation Needs Strong Public Schools", 1983; Series 7 (Box 2788, Folder 5)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"A Strong Nation Needs Strong Public Schools" [copy 2], 1983; Series 7 (Box 2788, Folder 6)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"A Strong Nation Needs Strong Public Schools" [copy 3], 1983; Series 7 (Box 2789, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Building Schools Together", 1987; Series 7 (Box 2789, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Educational Excellence: Our Nation's Strongest Defense", 1984; Series 7 (Box 2789, Folder 3)
    Contains 1 metal button, "AEW: American Education Week"
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Educational Excellence: Our Nation's Strongest Defense" [copy 2], 1984; Series 7 (Box 2789, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Education Can Turn Things Around", 1978; Series 7 (Box 2789, Folder 5)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Education Can Turn Things Around" [copy 2], 1978; Series 7 (Box 2789, Folder 6)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Get Involved", 1973; Series 7 (Box 2789, Folder 7)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Get Involved" [copy 2], 1973; Series 7 (Box 2789, Folder 8)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Make Education Top Priority", 1972; Series 7 (Box 2790, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Make Education Top Priority" [copy 2], 1972; Series 7 (Box 2790, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Our Future is in Our Schools", 1975; Series 7 (Box 2790, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Our Future is in Our Schools" [copy 2], 1975; Series 7 (Box 2790, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"School and Community: United for Excellence", 1986; Series 7 (Box 2791, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"School and Community: United for Excellence" [copy 2], 1986; Series 7 (Box 2791, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"The Schools are Yours: Help Take Care of Them", 1976; Series 7 (Box 2791, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"The Schools are Yours: Help Take Care of Them" [copy 2], 1976; Series 7 (Box 2791, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Stay Involved", 1974; Series 7 (Box 2791, Folder 5)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Stay Involved" [copy 2], 1974; Series 7 (Box 2791, Folder 6)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Teach All the Children", 1979; Series 7 (Box 2792, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Teach All the Children" [copy 2], 1979; Series 7 (Box 2792, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Working Together for Education", 1977; Series 7 (Box 2792, Folder 3)
  - American Education Week-Packet-"Working Together for Education" [copy 2], 1977; Series 7 (Box 2792, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week-Packets, 1938; Series 7 (Box 2793, Folder 1)
  - American Education Week-Packets and Other Material, 1940; Series 7 (Box 2793, Folder 2)
  - American Education Week Pamphlets, 1921-1973; Series 7 (Box 4092, Folder 4)
  - American Education Week Personal Growth Leaflets, 1941-1955; Series 7 (Box 4092, Folder 5)
  - American Education Week Planning, 1921-1966; Series 7 (Box 4092, Folder 6)